太他妈精彩了 你简直牛掰 老兄
This is fucking impressive. You hooked this shit up, friend.
THE SUB-MAN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
兄弟 我只想说演出太成功了
Hey, brother, I just wanna say you killed that shit.
老哥 你绝对嗨翻全场
My man. Absolutely killed that. For sure.
怎么样 兄弟 很高兴见到你
What's up, bro? Good to see you.
你现在可是如日中天
You're fuckin' imperial right now, OK?
我觉得"美国恶魔"是你最棒的专辑
I think American Diablo is your best album.
谢谢 兄弟们 非常感谢
Thanks, guys. Much obliged.
没事 老兄 太棒了...
All right, man. All right...
我们要跟上去吗
Are we supposed to follow him?
-该怎么办  -淡定
- What's gonna happen? - Just be cool.
他是你的小弟 对吧
So, this guy's your boy, right?
没错 听着
Yeah. Hey, listen,
我能跟你谈件事儿吗
can I talk to you about something?
说吧
Sure.
她来了 怎么样
Oh, here she comes. What's up?
看来他只是在减压
So he's just decompressing, apparently,
现在不愿意和外界联系
but he's really down to connect.
在减压是吧 他特么要坐船
Oh, he's decompressing? What, from his voyage
一路开到说唱海洋吗
to the bottom of the fuckin' rap ocean?
他的演出就是垃圾
His show was a shitty show.
但唱片公司为你们准备了包间
But the label got a room for you guys.
-这间  -不好意思 你叫什么名字
- Right here. - I'm sorry, what's your name?
-我叫杰西  -杰西 抱歉
- Jess. - Jess. Sorry.
你能提醒他一声
Can you just remind him
这个人管的公司
he's the guy that owns the company
是付他工资的唱片公司的
that owns the company that owns the label
-上级公司吗  -明白
- that pays his fucking ass? - Absolutely.
别照搬我的原话
Yeah, just don't say those words.
我的老天 瞧这个
Oh, my gosh, look at this.
大虾
Shrimp. Huh?
瞧瞧
Look at this.
这真空包装放在外面
Warmed in this airless box for like,
大概有六个钟头了吧
what, let's say six hours?
这团黏糊糊的东西 会好吃吗 试试
And this goo? Is this delicious fucking goo? Look at that.
听着 我有话要说
So, listen, I need to say something,
但一说出口可就没法收回了
but once I've said it I'll have said it,
虽然不是什么大事 不过比较微妙
and while it's not a big deal, it's delicate.
咋啦 你把公司搞砸了
What is it? You fucked the company?
还没来得及呢
I haven't fucked the company.
山达基教 到底啥事
Scientology? What is it?
山达基教: 黑社会性质的全球诈骗网络
咱们是朋友
Look, we're friends,
我们低谷的时候 我能信你的
we go back, I can trust you.
对吗
Right?
不能
No.
至少在钱上 我能相信你吗
Sure, but on money stuff, I can trust you?
不能
No.
我们在征集对我爸的不信任投票
Because we're calling a vote of no confidence on my dad.
你搞毛呢 兄弟
What the fuck, man.
这是当下最好的前进方式了
It's the best way forward right now.
太他妈乱了
This is fucking terrible.
你会把公司搞垮的 兄弟
Bro, you're gonna fuck the company.
你他妈在烧我钱呢 肯
You're fucking with my money, Ken.
我跟你说 这样做很公正
Look, I'm telling you, it's just cleanest.
他已经失控了
He's lost it.
他明天要去首都
He's going to D.C. Tomorrow
把我们的政治本钱气跑
to piss away our political capital
再把我们置于死地
and position us permanently in a dying sector.
-你觉得你能赢吗  -当然了
- Do you think you can win? - Of course.
全都定了 我在通知你 不是争取你
It's finished. I'm informing you, not courting you.
我还要和剩下来的人共事
Because I have to work with whoever's left.
没错 和我一起
Right. With me.
说好了吗
So are we good?
我能指望你投未来队一票吗
Can I count on your vote for Team Future?
我能向你保证 我在精神上
I can promise you that I am spiritually
情感上和伦理上
and emotionally and ethically
和道义上支持胜者
and morally behind whoever wins.
翻译: 奶啾
翻译: 我的后面是猪精
翻译: Shirley Q
翻译: 李木木
翻译: 海顿
翻译: 豆
时间轴: 阿布
特效: 雨人
后期&压制: Jason肖
校对:渡渡
校对：宇宙万宝路
继承
第一季 第６集
"你站在哪一边"
监制: 宇宙万宝路
怎么了
What's the matter?
我很火大 因为我要像个快递员一样
I'm pissed because I have to come down to him
到他面前谈事 为什么他就不能过来
like a fuckin' FedEx guy. Why can't he come to us?
大概因为他是总统
Well, I guess he's the president.
操蛋的小瘪葡萄干加州人
Fuckin' Californian shrunken little raisin.
我见过十多个他们这种人
I've seen ten of 'em.
他基本也就实习生的水平
He's basically a fuckin' intern.
你跟得上节奏吗 卡尔
Are you OK, Karl, on all this?
能 当然能
Yeah. Sure. Yeah.
-法律流程也行吗  -行
- On the law? - Yeah.
格丽大致跟我说过了...
Gerri walked me through it too, so...
我倒希望在这的是她不是你
I wish she was here and not you.
谢谢你
Well, thank you.
她得待在纽约准备董事会会议...
She has to stay in the city for board meeting prep, so...
我开玩笑呢 卡尔
It was a joke, Karl.
我猜要是我说在告尔朵里放杏仁[浓缩奶咖]
And I'm guessing if I say cortado with almond,
你大概会觉得我是个混蛋吧
you're gonna look like I'm some kind of jerk, right?
请给我来一杯清咖 谢谢你
I will have a black coffee, please and thank you.
这里安全吗
Is this safe?
这里应该不会碰到其他人
I don't think we're gonna bump into anyone here.
斯图伊怎么说
So how'd it go with Stewy?
进展不错 他同意了
It went great. He's in.
行 那太好了
OK. Well, that's great.
这样看来我们情况不错
Yeah. So I think we're all good.
打开和服: 未来新合伙人披露某一项目
或本公司的内部运作情况
咱们向公众... 打开和服之前
Shall I just... run it one more time
需要最后再捋一遍吗
before we open our kimonos in public?
洛根
Logan.
投票一旦提出
Once the vote is proposed,
他就要回避... 也就是出局了
he's recused... out of the game.
现在有肯德尔 罗曼 弗兰克 三票赞成
So we have Kendall, Roman, Frank. Three votes in favor.
还有阿沙 你的红人 没问题吧
And Asha. Your pet. That's good?
坚如磐石[没问题] 已经明确表态了
Rock solid. Already floated and noted.
好
Right.
保罗 戴维 塔图...
Paul, Dewi, Datu...
他们是守旧派 会跟洛根走
they're old guard, they'll go Logan.
当然 我... 好吧
Yeah, well, sure. I mean... but sure.
尤恩叔叔
OK, Uncle Ewan, uh,
还是能争取下的 对吧
he's still a possible, right?
你可以借宿怨再点把火
Um, you could maybe stoke the old resentments?
麦克白夫人[冷酷又有野心] 小心思挺多呀
Lady Macbeth, gettin' your little fuckin' screwdriver in.
这他妈不是儿戏[泰迪熊野餐] 罗曼
It's not a fucking teddy bear's picnic, Roman,
-这是场屠杀  -劳伦斯呢
- it's a massacre. - Lawrence?
爸会把沃尔特拆分出售
Dad would sell Vaulter for parts.
劳伦斯要疯了才不跟我们投
Lawrence would be crazy not to vote with me.
别忘了劳伦斯讨厌你
Except Lawrence hates you.
现在三票赞成 五票反对 还有三票不清楚
We have three for Logan, five against, three unknowns.
瞎扯淡 我们加把劲 劳伦斯就站我们队了
Come on, this is bullshit. Look, we push, Lawrence is ours,
尤恩能站我们队 伊罗娜也能
Ewan could be ours, Ilona could be ours.
格丽不能投票 但她能代表上级管理层发言
Gerri can't vote, but she can talk for senior management.
这不就完了 我们太小心了
This is done. There's being cautious,
所以浪费了这么多时间
and there's being fucking time-wasters.
你要想我赞成 就得考虑最坏的情况
If you want me to do this, you gotta look worst case.
劳伦斯 尤恩 伊罗娜 都得表态
Lawrence, Ewan, Ilona, all in play.
再有一票就能赢了
One more makes us sure winners.
好吧... 我们去争取劳伦斯
Yeah. We, uh... we hit Lawrence.
我接到电话 核反应堆关停了
I got the call. The nuclear reactor is sealed off.
-感染者也被击毙  -太好了
- The infected have been shot. - Oh, that's great.
太好了 谢谢你
That's great. Thank you.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
-没事了  -好的 好
- We're good. - OK. OK.
-再见  -再见
- Goodbye. - Bye.
-再也别见了  -希望如此
- Yeah. Goodbye forever. - Hope so.
...三个人
...three men
拥有全美一半的财富
to own half the wealth of America.
我刚得知 麻烦都结了
I have just been given the all-clear.
感觉又能呼吸了
Ohh! I feel I can breathe again.
讲真 亲爱的 就好像一只四百公斤的大猩猩
Honestly, honey, it's like this 900-pound gorilla
终于停止干我了
has finally stopped fucking me.
是我不想知道的那事儿吧
Now, is this the thing I don't want to know about?
是的 这事儿没了
Yeah. And it's gone.
我觉得我没事了 没事了
I think I'm good. I think I'm good.
格雷格 我 问题解决得天衣无缝
Greg. Me. The circle's tight.
他很棒 他就是我的R2小兵[星战中的正义方小机器人]
He's good. He's my little R2 unit.
我不知道
I don't know.
我不... 这... 我他妈不知道
Arrgh! I don't... This... I don't fucking know!
还要再跟着她吗
Should I stick with her?
她有总统相吗
Is that a president?
大概吧 我不知道
Maybe. I don't know.
我也不想当大男子主义的新郎
Now, not to be Groomzilla,
但我们能谈谈婚宴菜单吗
but can we talk about menus?
我非常 非常喜欢科莫湖
'Cause I really, really love Lake Como,
可是我担心起雾
but I'm worried about the fog.
我很清楚人是不会变的
One thing is, people don't change.
候选人不会改变
You know, a candidate can't change.
你再怎么美化她 夸大她 包装她
You can primp and plump and repackage,
但你要是想从根本上改变一个人
but if you want to change someone fundamentally,
-没门  -我们应该按照...
- forget it. - So, should we go...
传统上流纽约风格来办吗
very old New York classy?
是这样 我...
Oh. Yeah. Uh, I...
抱歉 我前几天
Sorry, I had a pretty
跟我妈在电话里闹不开心了
shitty phone call with my mom the other day,
为了缓和一下气氛 我就说我们可能会
and just to smooth things over I said that we might
回英格兰办婚礼
have the wedding back in England.
-你说什么  -对
- You what? - Yeah.
-你觉得这很严重吗  -开什么玩笑 小西 没门儿
- Is that a biggie for you? - Excuse me, Shiv. Fuck.
汤姆 这只是个婚礼啊 策划师们会办好的
Tom, it's just a wedding. The planners will figure it out.
-"只是个婚礼"吗 小西  -对呀
- "Just a wedding"? Shiv. - Yeah.
-这是我们的婚礼  -汤姆...
- It's our wedding! - Oh, Tom...
-一辈子就这一次  -我现在没空想这事
- It only happens once. - I can't do this right now.
-汤姆  -好吧 先别...
- Tom. - OK. No...
我正在努力工作
I'm trying to think about work.
我很期待婚礼
And I'm looking forward to it,
可就是没法投入 特别是对所有细节
but I just can't get into it all, all the details.
这个婚礼可能在英格兰办 可也能不是
I mean, the wedding might be in England, but it might not.
好吧 好吧 对不起 抱歉
OK, OK, sorry, sorry.
那我去搞定劳伦斯
So, I'll take Lawrence,
你去稳住其他人 可以吧
and you firm up the others, yeah?
没问题 我能搞定他
That's OK. I got him.
别太天真 我了解他
No, I know the guy.
我去的每一个虚伪至极的派对
I see him at every fucking fakers party,
营业开幕式都能瞧见他
phony soft opening that I go to.
都市丽男: 爱好时尚和购物等的异性恋男子
我和他就像两颗夹在都市丽男荚中的豌豆
We're like two peas in a metrosexual think pod.
到底做不做
Look, are we doing this?
还他妈要不要合作管理一家公司了
Are we running a fucking company together, or what?
虽然我像个笑话 但不意味着我他妈是个小丑
Just 'cause I like a joke doesn't mean I'm a fucking clown.
小罗 我只是想...
Look, Rome, I'm just trying to...
-我明白了  -我知道你不是个小丑
- I got it. - I know you're not a clown.
-当然了  -这很微妙
- I'm not. - It's delicate.
这微妙吗 我自己都没发现
Oh, it's delicate? I didn't realize
这些微妙之处
it was delicate, the little nuances.
劳伦斯恨死你了 兄弟 真的
Lawrence fuckin' hates you, man, he does.
-那他喜欢你吗  -没错
- And he likes you? - Yeah.
他是喜欢我 是个人都喜欢我
He likes me. People like me.
我就像个斗牛士 所有人都想来顶我
I look like a matador and everyone wants to fuck me.
我一直在他身边观察他 我了解这个人
I see him around. I know the guy.
-相信我  -好吧
- Trust me. - OK.
格丽说有很多迹象
Gerri says there are multiple indicators
表明他对我们的扩张是支持的
he wants to be sympathetic to our expansion.
你也这么想吗
You think so?
一旦他批准
If he waves this through,
就能得到上百家当地电视台
he gets hundreds of local TV stations
然后它们都有义务夸他是个多伟大的人
And most amenable to talking about what a great fuckin' guy he is.
他只需要做足准备
He just needs to be prepared
面对小小的政治压力
to take a little political heat is all.
再过四年 我们就能成为新闻界的宝洁公司了
Four more years, we're Proctor & Gamble of the news.
汤姆 我要去华盛顿了
Hey. Tom. I'm heading to Washington.
你介意我错过晚餐吗 我要搞清楚乔伊丝的底细
Do you mind if I miss dinner? I need to figure out about Joyce.
不会的 宝贝 没关系
No, sweetheart, that's fine.
如果你需要想清楚自己对乔伊丝的投入
If you need to think about your commitment to Joyce,
那就去吧 做下去 快去华盛顿吧
then go, do it. Go to Washington.
我只是想知道自己的赌注押对了没
Yeah, I just wondered if I picked the right horse.
没关系 我明白 真的
No, I get it, I do. Yeah.
把她查得彻彻底底吧 宝贝
Slide her under the X-ray machine, baby.
-好的 我爱你 挂了  -我也爱你 拜
- OK. Love you. Bye. - You, too. Bye.
好哇 兄弟
Hey hey, guy.
好哇
Hey hey.
一切都好吗 格雷格
Hey. Everything OK, Greg?
-好 当然好了  -确定吗  -确定
- Yeah. Yeah. - Sure? - Sure.
那就好
Good.
很好
Good good.
其实你能
You know, you can,
你能对我畅所欲言 知道吗
you can talk to me about anything. You know?
当然 我会... 谢谢
Oh, yeah. Well, I... Thanks.
你棒极的... 资源
Fantastic... resource.
好吧
Ok, ok.
其实小西要去华盛顿了
So, Shiv is going to Washington,
所以 今晚我带你出去怎么样
so why don't, tonight, why don't I take you out?
不想吗
No?
你说真的吗
What, for real?
我以为你会说
I thought you were gonna say
"带你出去 然后把你打得屁滚尿流"
"Take you out and beat the shit out of you,"
或者"带你出去 然后
or "Take you out and put
在你白痴的头上来一枪"
a bullet through your dumb fuckin' brain,"
或者其他那些 搞笑的话
or something else, you know, funny like that.
不 格雷格 我又不是什么吃人的野兽
No, Greg, I'm not some beast.
好吧 其实 我终于拿到工资了...
Well, actually, I finally got paid...
好啊 真好
Attaboy. OK.
他们好像不会付这里的电费
It's like they're not paying the light bill here,
但我的确拿到工资了
but, but I actually got paid,
我还在想也许可以去
and I was thinking about maybe going to,
你去过"加州披萨厨房"吗
have you ever visited California Pizza Kitchen?
没有 天呢 并没有
No. Dear Lord, no.
他们家东西很好吃 汤姆
It's pretty delicious, Tom.
不 不 并不好吃 格雷格
No. No, it isn't, Greg.
你可能认为好吃 但...
I mean, you might think it tastes delicious, but...
他们能做我超爱吃的法式鸡肉面
They make a Cajun chicken linguini just how I like it.
可这并不能成为你爱这家店的理由
But that's not how you're supposed to like it.
好吧 你的味觉似乎还没发育成熟
OK, you probably have quite an undereducated palate.
那就出去吃吧 我来调教你
So, let's go out, and I'll teach you.
我来示范一下怎么做有钱人 行吗 会很好玩的
And I'll show you how to be rich. OK? It'll be fun.
他就在沿走廊那里等您 罗伊先生
He'll be just along the hallway here, Mr. Roy.
我来过这儿
I have been here before,
我也知道走廊是干嘛的
and I do know how hallways work.
会有人即刻来见您
Someone will be with you shortly.
真是不着边际的废话 对吧
What a fuckin' song and dance, eh?
罗伊先生 非常抱歉
Mr. Roy. I am so sorry,
总统传达了他最真诚的歉意
but the president passes on his sincere apologies.
他正在处理一些国土安全的事务
He's currently dealing with a matter of homeland security.
他相信您会理解的 他将会安排
He's sure you'll understand, but he's going to need to offer
代替面孔参与此次讨论
an alternative face for this discussion.
"代替面孔" 这他妈是什么意思
"Alternative face," What the fuck does that mean?
如果我脱掉裤子 也能给你看一张代替面孔
If I drop my pants, I can show you an alternative face.
这听着如何
How does that sound?
我这是被怠慢了吗
Have I been snubbed?
查清楚我是不是被怠慢了
Find out if I've been snubbed.
我觉得您多虑了
I don't think you've been snubbed.
老子被怠慢了吗 给我他妈的查清楚
Is this a snubbing?! Just fucking find out!
老天 威姆士丹
Holy shit. Wamsgans!
眼圈怎么黑了
A fuckin' black eye?
你该去看看另一个人
You should see the other guy.
那个用屌戳你眼睛的人吗
The guy who jammed his dick in your eye?
其实是
Let's just say, uh,
我和小西在床上 然后...
I was in bed, with Shiv, so...
不会吧 她打了你
What? She punched you?
不是
No.
只是进行得有点过火了
Things just get a little hot and heavy.
有点儿疯狂 所以...
A little freaky-deaky. So...
上我俩的妹妹吗 太酷了 兄弟
Fuckin' our sister? That's cool, man.
对 但谈这事还有点奇怪呢
Yeah, it's kinda weird when you talk about that.
不 我觉得这是真的酷
No, I think it's really cool.
说说看 上我俩的妹妹是啥感觉
Like, what's it like, like, to bang our sister?
发生什么了 告诉我呗
So what's goin' on? Clue me in.
我们刚说完了 兄弟
we just finished, bud.
对滴 是这样 我要去
Yup. Yeah, I'm gonna go, uh,
去吃头鹿啥的
eat a fucking elk or something.
回见
See ya later.
那什么 汤姆
Oh, hey, Tom.
我只想说 我知道你帮我处理了很多
Just to say I know you've been eating a lot of shit for me
我自己都不知情的麻烦
that I don't know about,
我很感激
and I appreciate that.
我想让你知道 我欣赏你
I want you to know, I like you.
你是肯德尔队的人 兄弟
You're Team Kendall, man.
虽然在走下坡路
Lot of stuff goin' down,
可你依旧在队伍里
but you're on the team.
谢谢你 兄弟
Thanks, brother.
敬我们
Here's to us.
To us.
我需要问些事儿
so I do need to ask something,
可是...
but, um...
咱们很铁 对吧
we're cool, yeah?
我们就是他妈的破坏者 是吧
Like, we're fuckin' disruptors, Yeah?
没错
Yeah.
不过...
But, um...
如果我...
what would you say...
如果我告诉你明天
what would you say if I told you
将会有一场不信任投票 你会怎么想
that there was gonna be a vote of no confidence tomorrow?
踢掉老家伙 新人上位
Kick out the old man, in with the new guard.
小罗和小肯当家
Romey and the homey.
你和肯德尔在计划杀掉你爸吗
You and Kendall are thinking of killing your dad?
-这...  -这不成希腊悲剧了吗
- Well... - That's a little Greek tragedy.
对啊 "俄狄浦斯王"
Yeah, Oedipus.
我说过我要上玛西娅吗
Did I say that I was going to fuck Marcia?
注: 俄狄浦斯杀父娶母
没 可我肯定会做的 因为她性感极了
No. Although I definitely would, 'cause she's hot.
但那是 你懂的 那是第二阶段的事了
But that's, you know, that's like phase two.
-来了  -来了
- Hey. - Hey.
很抱歉我迟到了
I'm sorry I'm late.
没关系 别担心
Yeah, no. No worries.
这地方变了
This place has changed.
额... 没错
Uh... yeah.
我是说 其实所有事都变了
I mean, well, e-everything changes.
我们也是
We've changed.
我没听错吧 小西·罗伊也会多愁善感了
What's this? Shiv Roy goes soulful.
这可不像你
Does not suit you.
就像你穿了高领毛衣 贴了胡子一样怪
It's like you're wearing a turtleneck and a stick-on mustache.
好吧 没错
All right, yeah.
我还有感情的
Well, I do have feelings.
那么 祝贺米勒参议员
So, congratulations on Senator Miller.
谢谢
Thank you.
这不算是正宗的南部战略
Not exactly the fuckin' Southern Strategy,
能招来一群犹太人 黑人 和媒体学者
gettin' a bunch of Jews, blacks, and media studies professors
去纽约州投民主党 可还是能...
to vote in a Democrat in New York state, but still...
去你的 你也瞧见数字了
Fuck you. You've seen the numbers.
是的 其实有很多方式来分析这些数字
Yeah, there's a number of ways of analyzing the numbers.
丑闻都要火烧眉毛了 我也都处理好了
I did a fucking good job, in the teeth of a scandal.
在这种关键时期 我他妈表现得不能再精彩了
At this point in the cycle, I knocked it out of the fucking park.
所以这杯要敬我自己
So here's to me.
吉尔伊维斯共和国怎么样了
How's everything in the People's Republic of Gil Eavis?
棒极了
Amazing.
咱们开门见山吧 小西 这是要干嘛
So, go on, Shiv, what is this?
好吧 其实...
OK, uh, well...
我希望你能考虑加入我们
I want you to think about joining us.
-加入我和乔伊丝吧  -为什么
- Me and Joyce. - Why?
因为我需要队伍里有一颗老鼠屎
Because I need a piece of shit on the team.
你觉得呢
What do you think?
我觉得... 这真是好主意吗 我俩凑一块儿
I think... is it a good idea? You and me?
-为什么不呢  -从以往的经验来看
- Uh, yeah. Why? - Historically speaking,
只要咱俩凑一块不滚床单都难
we found it quite hard not to fuck each other.
见到你真好... 刚约上就见到了
It's great to see you... on such short notice.
嘘 吃饭
Shush. Eat.
我差不多吃完了 外公
I finished most of 'em, Grandpa.
你母亲说你没有钱
Your mother says you don't have any money.
直到前段时间 但其实
Until recently, but actually, um,
我工资到账了
my pay came through.
现在我非常富有
And now I'm incredibly rich.
真的吗
Really?
我相信你一定会非常开心的
Well, uh, I'm sure you're going to be very happy.
谢谢你
Thank you.
她还告诉我要喂饱你
She also told me to feed you,
所以吃光
so eat up.
老实说
Whew. Honestly,
我想我的胃已经缩水了
I think my stomach might have shrunk
在我... 贫穷的那段时间
during my... my period of poverty.
这个城市的浪费简直可憎
The waste in this city is obscene.
吃光它
Finish it.
你怎么过来... 到城里了
So, how come you're here... you're in town,
我可以问一下吗
uh, if I may ask?
你是个大人了 "据说"
You're a grownup, allegedly.
所以我就直接说了
So here's what grownups do.
肯德尔将进行不信任投票
Kendall is gonna call for a vote of no confidence
在下次董事会上反对他父亲
against his own father at the next board meeting.
听起来像个大事
S-Sounds like a huge deal,
但这只是走程序还是...
but it's just procedure or...
这就是一种肆无忌惮的自私行为
It's a wanton act of egregious selfishness.
与我对这个下流之家鄙视的
In keeping with everything else I've come to loathe
一切事情同类
about this rat's nest of a family.
是的 对
Right. Right.
你会告诉洛根吗
So are you gonna tell Logan?
我会闭紧我的嘴巴远离纷争
I'm gonna keep my snout of the trough,
多谢 但算了吧
thank you very much.
我给你的建议是 少管闲事[划好自己的独木舟]
And my advice to you is: paddle your own canoe.
喂
Hello?
肯德尔吗
Kendall?
玛西娅
Marcia.
我在想如果你不忙的话
I was wondering, if you're not busy,
你是否介意与你父亲共进晚餐
if you don't mind joining your father for dinner?
他叫我共进晚餐了吗
Did he ask to have dinner with me?
是的
Yeah.
他独自在家
He's home alone,
我有个非去不可的活动
and I have something I cannot miss.
只有他跟我吗
just him and me?
是的 时间不凑巧吗
Yeah. Is it a bad time?
你有什么计划吗
Do you have something planned?
当然没有
Uh, no. Of course.
没有 我会去的
Um, no, I'm-- I'm around.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我留了点清蒸鱼
I've left some steamed fish.
非常感谢
Merci beaucoup.
好的
OK.
正是
Exactly.
安康鱼: 深海鱼 其肝味道鲜美被称为"海中鹅肝"
我吃这家的安康鱼时
When I had their monkfish,
还以为自己要同时拉裤子 呕吐和高潮
I thought I was gonna shit, puke and cum all at once.
听起来... 很美味
That sounds... delicious.
但其实我没什么食欲
Although I don't actually have much of an appetite.
你最好赶紧找到胃口
Well, you better find one quick,
因为这是全城最高档的餐厅之一
'cause this is one of the most exclusive popups in the city,
而且咱们要品尝整张试味菜单
and we're having the full tasting menu.
怎么... 为什么酒单上没有价格
How come the... the wine list doesn't have any prices?
因为它们巨贵无比
Because they're obscene.
听着 这就是有钱的好处 懂吗
Look, here's the thing about being rich, OK?
感觉太他妈好了
It's fucking great.
懂吗 就像是变成了超级英雄 只是还要更好
OK? It's like being a superhero, only better.
你可以为所欲为
You get to do what you want,
当局不会真的碰你
the authorities can't really touch you,
你可以穿戏服 但是由阿玛尼设计的
you get to wear a costume, but it's designed by Armani,
并且还不会看着像个混蛋
and it doesn't make you look like a prick.
好吧 好吧
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-谢谢你  -谢谢你
- Thank you. - Thank you.
如果我站你的队 你的愿景是什么
If I was going to come in with you, what's your vision?
是我和肯德尔的愿景
Well, it's me and Kendall.
别他妈管肯德尔 行吗
Fuck Kendall. OK?
你 你的愿景是什么
You. What's your vision?
你知道吗
You know what?
前几天我去了一家书店
I ended up in a book shop the other day,
然后就开始狂笑
and I just started laughing.
然后呢
Ok.
我看着所有书 堆满了墙
I was looking at all the books cramming up all the walls,
我就想到 那些从前的日子
and I just thought, you know, about the olden days,
所有的修道院和圣经
all the fucking monasteries and the Bibles
还有布道辞 "耶稣说这个了吗"
and the sermons and the "Did Jesus say this?
"你是那个意思吗"
And "Do you mean that?"
所有话语和诸如此类的事物
and all the words and what have you.
都不见了
All gone.
没人他妈的在乎
No one gives a fuck.
你是说我们将进入后文学时代
You're saying we're going post-literate.
人们将会阅读
People are gonna read,
但旧世界 已经消失了
but the old world, it's gone.
纸质世界消失了 新闻消失了
Papers, gone. News, gone.
"九点准时收看ABS电视台 告诉你该怎么想"
"Tune in to ABS at nine to be told what to think."
不 结束了
No. Over.
口水化信息才是重点 伙计
It's all about the morsels, man.
喂我美味的口水化信息就够了
Feed me the fucking tasty morsels.
保持我的兴趣 这就是我们的方向
Keep me interested. That is where we're headed.
绝妙中心产生的美味口水化信息
Tasty morsels from groovy hubs.
绝妙中心产生的... 美味口水化信息
Tasty morsels... from groovy hubs.
听着 伙计
Um, look, man,
我很笨 但我也很聪明
I'm dumb, but I'm smart.
我太笨不知道怎么修整公司
I'm too dumb to know how to fix our whole company.
我的注意广度不大
I don't have the attention span.
这可能是我一生中发生的
This is probably the most interesting thing
最有趣的事情了
that's happened in my whole life,
而我还在想六件其他的事
and I'm thinking about six other things.
但我足够聪明 知道什么需要改变
But I am smart enough to know what needs changing,
而且足够聪明去找到
and I'm smart enough to spot the people
能帮助我们的人 劳伦斯
who can help us, Lawrence.
所以你加入吗
So are you in?
我站在变革的这一边
I'm on the side of change.
对 当然啦
Yeah, you are.
抱歉 操
Sorry-- Oh, fuck.
介意我接这个电话吗
Mind if I take this?
去吧
Go ahead.
抱歉 朋友们 保持性感
Sorry, fellas. Keep it sexy.
啥事
Yeah?
玛西娅要我和爸共进晚餐
Marcia asked me to have dinner with Dad.
-他知道了 他知道吗  -我不知道
- He knows. Does he know? - I don't know.
他提我了吗
Did he mention me?
劳伦斯怎么说
What did Lawrence say?
他加入
Uh, he's in.
来真的吗
For real?
是的 真的 操你的
Yes, for real. Fuck you.
很好 好的
Nice. OK.
太好了 谢谢
OK, great. Thanks.
老天啊
Oh, Jesus.
现在又要上什么
What-- What now?
-蒿雀  -蒿雀是什么
- Ortolan. - What's ortolan?
一种油炸的鸣禽 你把它整个吃掉
It is a deep-fried songbird. You eat it whole.
-我的天...  -真是一种罕见的特权
- Oh, my God... - This is a rare privilege.
好像也是非法的
And it's also kind of illegal.
-我已经有...  -这是头戴的
- Oh, I have a... - For the head.
确切目的仍在争论
The exact purpose is debated.
有人说这是为了掩盖羞耻
Some say it's to mask the shame;
其他人认为能够提升快感
others, to heighten the pleasure.
我的天呐
Oh, my God.
太好吃了
That is so good.
你吃了吗 格雷格
Did you eat it yet, Greg?
-还没  -吃啊 格雷格
- Not yet, no. - Eat it, Greg!
它真的风味... 很独特
Um, it's a rather... unique flavor.
对 它是种强烈的味觉冲击 我的朋友
Yeah, it's the gamy, brainy hit, my friend.
我们能再来点酒吗
Can we have some more wine, please?
你想引诱我吗 汤姆
You trying to seduce me, Tom?
是的 格雷格 我想
Yes, I am! Yes, I am, Greg.
我们所见的一切
All the things we've seen,
所做的一切...
all the things we've done...
都是在同一条战线上的 伙计
we're in this together, man.
好的 这...
OK. Is that...
你带我出来就是 为了那件事吗
Is that what this is, this is about the thing?
我们有种联系
We have a bond.
-有吗  -是的 当然
- You do? - Yeah, sure.
我曾经也是个局外人
I was an outsider once.
来自圣保罗的年轻人 独自在大城市很难的
Young guy from St. Paul, alone in the big city, and it was hard.
于是你创造了一种保护壳
And you create this kind of protective shell,
但内心深处我们都是... 赤裸的小海龟
but underneath, we're all just little... nudie turtles.
好吧
Ok.
我得跟你说实话
I gotta level with you,
因为如果我再吃鸣禽 就要吐了
because if I eat any more songbirds, I'm gonna hurl.
我外公今天已经请我吃过晚饭了
My grandpa already bought me dinner tonight.
你外公吗 他来纽约做什么
Your grandpa? What's he doing in New York?
他明天要来参加这个对洛根的不信任投票
He's come down for this vote of no confidence in Logan tomorrow.
你知道这件事吗
Did you know about that?
什么 你认真的吗
What? You serious?
是的 他专程来投票的
Yeah, he's come down especially to vote.
这是大事 对吧
It's a big deal, right?
是的 等下 等等
Yeah. Hold on. Hold on.
你说过你想要我... 但其实你不想
You say you want me... but really, you don't.
你比我自己还了解我 真令人兴奋
It's so exciting when you know more about me than I do.
你要我加入是需要我的棱角 因为她优势不强
You want me for my edge, 'cause she's not edgy enough.
你应该给吉尔这样的赢家工作
You should be workin' for a winner like Gil.
你知道我和你相比
You know I'm a considerably
是更加成功的政治战略家
more successful political strategist than you are.
小西 你拿你拥有的东西努力
Shiv, you work with what you got,
而你拥有的是...
and what you got is...
我培养了乔伊丝三年
I've been grooming Joyce for three years.
-吸引了每个人  -正是这样
- Appeals to everyone. - Exactly.
也就是说对任何人都没有吸引力 她很好
Which is a little like appealing to no one. She's nice.
对别人说这句话是很可怕的
That is a horrible thing to say about anyone.
听着 肯德尔告诉我你要嫁给...
Look, Kendall told me how you're marrying this...
来自曲棍球镇玉米喂大的男人
guy, this corn-fed basic from hockey town.
-是的 汤姆 他人很棒  -那当然
- Yeah, Tom. He's a great guy. - Sure.
顶着方块头的很棒的人
Great guy with the square head.
你还在为这位漂亮的黑人女士工作
And you're workin' for the nice black lady.
-你想证明什么  -你他妈真是个混蛋
- What are you trying to prove? - You're such a fucking prick.
你应该跟像我一样刺激的混蛋在一起
You should be with an exciting bastard like me.
我试过和你玩 但你搞砸了
I tried playing with you, and you broke.
先生 你父亲在书房接听电话
Sir. Your father's on a call in the den.
他请求你稍等片刻
He asked if you'd wait a moment.
好
Oh, sure.
汤姆 有事儿能明天说吗
Tom? Uh, hey, can this wait till tomorrow?
这消息你会想听的 尤恩到纽约了
You're gonna want to hear this. Ewan is in town,
而且他知道了 他专门来投票的
and he knows, and he's come to vote.
什么 等... 等下
What? Hold... Hold on.
你哪来的消息
Who's your source?
我不能暴露消息来源
Uh, I can't reveal my sources.
是格雷格
But it's Greg.
好吧 汤姆
OK. Uh, Tom,
你一个字都不能走漏 好吗
you do not breathe a word of this, OK?
我嘴封死了
My lips are sealed.
好的 谢了 汤姆 我很感激
All right. Thanks, Tom. I appreciate it.
不是什么大事 肯德尔队万岁
It's not a big deal. Team Kendall.
天啊 天啊 确实要发生了
My God. My God! It's actually happening.
正在发生
It's happening.
军队要占领萨达姆的宫殿了 老兄
The troops are taking Saddam's palace, man.
到明天这个时候 你和我...
This time tomorrow, you and me...
我就能... 我就能是...
I could... I could be like the...
我就是这个公司第三重要的人物了
I could be like the third most important guy in the company.
这就像攻占巴士底狱一样
I mean, it's the storming of the Bastille.
吃蛋糕庆祝吧...
Let us eat cake. I mean...
我不知道我们在说什么
I don't know what we're talking about.
谢了 理查德
Thanks, Richard.
晚上好 爸
Hey, Dad.
好
Hey.
你不该吃这种垃圾
You shouldn't eat this shit.
你又不是我老板
You're not the boss of me.
你想谈谈吗 玛西娅说你... 想要见我
Did you want to talk? Marcia said you... wanted to see me.
玛西娅
Marcia.
是啊 她在忙她的勾当
Yeah, she's got her own game goin' on.
什么意思
What does that mean?
你清楚什么意思
You know what it means.
你有你的勾当
You've got your game goin' on.
我也有我的
I've got my game.
什么... 什么 什么是你的勾当
What... What's, uh, what's your game?
人人都有自己的勾当
Everybody's got a game.
到底什么情况
So what's goin' on?
有什么行动 有什么故事
What's the action? What's the story?
什么情况
What's goin' on?
听说我跟总统的会面了没
You heard about my meet?
你听说我被人怠慢了吗
You heard it was a snub?
什么...
What? Uh... Oh.
对 我听说了...
Yeah, I heard, um...
我听说真的有安全警报
Uh, I heard real security alert,
但谁知道呢 很难解读
but who knows, it's tough to read.
妈的
Oh, fuck.
我得做点儿什么处理这件事
I could do something about this.
吃吗
Ok?
我都不知道多久...
Haven't had one of these in, uh...
没吃过这些了
I don't even know.
你要吃吗
You gonna eat it?
当然 我当然要吃
Yeah, I'm gonna eat it.
太好了
Hey, good.
-干杯  -干杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
操了
Oh, fuck!
每次都他妈这样
Every fuckin' time!
谢了 老兄 谢了
Thanks, man. Thanks.
需要我去端几杯啤酒吗
Should I get us some beers?
不 不需要 这是整瓶服务 我点了伏特加
No, no. No need. Bottle service. I ordered vodka.
来吧
Come on.
来吧 老兄
Whoa! Go ahead, man.
好吧 这就是你的日常吗
Hey! So this is what you do?
你来夜店 然后直奔夜店里的
You, like, go to a club, and then you come to, like,
这种又不像夜店的角落吗
this other part where the club sort of isn't?
是的 没错 就是这样
Yeah! Yeah, that's it!
开一瓶酒就一万三
This is 2,000 bucks a pop.
为什么
Why?
不为什么 我们就是被坑了
No reason! We're being totally ripped off!
这是金子吧... 这掺了金箔吧
Is this gold... Is this gold leaf?
没错 把金子喝掉吧 我的朋友
Uh-huh. Drink the gold, my friend.
过会儿咱们就能撒出纯金的尿
And then later you and I can have a 24-karat piss.
有新消息吗
Any news?
我们争取到劳伦斯了
Um, we have Lawrence.
这能让我睡踏实些
That'll make me sleep easier.
如果我能睡着的话 可我不能
If I can sleep. Which I won't.
我应该给萨丽塔打个电话
I think I'm just gonna call Sarita
打探下伊罗娜是不是不投票
and check Ilona's out of the action.
有必要吗
Oh, do we need?
你不担心会打草惊蛇吗
You're not worried that could stir things?
我只想面面俱到
Just to cover all the bases.
弗兰克
Hey, Frank?
听着 这... 这件事...
Listen, is... is this...
客观来看 这样... 是不是糟透了
Is this, like, objectively... horrible?
我们还是可以等一等
You know, w-we could hold off.
可以下一季度再提案...
We could put this together next quarter...
小肯 这事由你牵头
Ken. You made this happen.
能聚齐五个人
It's hard enough to get
吃一顿吃晚餐已经很不容易了
five people together for a fuckin' dinner.
你可能再没有这样的机会了
You might never get another shot.
而且这样做是正确的
And it's the right thing to do.
强硬起来
Strength.
你是个好儿子
You're a good son.
晚安 小肯
Night, Ken.
晚安
Goodnight.
-喂  -萨丽塔 你好
- Hello? - Sarita, hey.
很抱歉这么晚打来 我...
Sorry to call so late. I...
我只是在想 然后... 然后...
You know, I was just, uh, thinking, and... and...
听到你的声音我很高兴
It's nice to hear your voice.
是 听到你的声音我也很高兴
Yeah, it's nice to hear your voice.
我很过意不去
I don't know, I felt bad,
所以想打来问问... 你妈妈的近况
and I wanted to check in... on your mom.
明天的董事会投票
Uh, I assume she can't make it
我想她没法到场吧 真可惜
to the board meeting tomorrow, sadly.
没错 我得挂了 肯德尔
No. I have to go, Kendall.
那么 再跟我说说白薯头先生吧
So, tell me more about Mr. Potato Head.
汤姆吗
Tom?
他是个... 他棒极了
He's a... He's amazing.
好吧 我很满意
Well, I'm pleased.
-可... 真的很棒  -小西
- Uh, but... It is great. - Shiv.
你正试图说服我 你确实在这样做
You're convincing me. You are.
这类似于一种... 令人厌倦的不断重复
It's the constant sort of... weary repetition.
-"汤姆好棒棒"  -他就是棒
- "Tom's great." - He is.
我们今晚不会滚床单吧
We're not gonna fuck tonight, right?
你知道我也要结婚了
You know I'm getting married, too.
真的吗
Oh, really.
跟车模还是三流女演员
Car model or failed actress?
真毒 露出真面目了
Ouch. There she is.
她其实是名法国医生
She's actually a French doctor.
蛮好的
That's nice.
但这并不意味着我们不能做点儿别的
I mean, it doesn't mean we can't do other stuff.
理论上来说
Theoretically.
我三月结婚
I'm getting married in March.
我五月结婚
I'm getting married in May.
-这又不是比赛  -当然不是 没错
- It's not a competition. - Sure. Yeah.
但我们中只有一个在丁香花开的季节结婚
But only one of us is getting married in lilac season,
而这个人不是你
and it's not you.
-来吧  -什么
- Come on. - What?
我得说我正感觉到...
I have to say I am feeling...
你感觉到什么 纳特
You're feeling what, Nate?
我们可以在各自的房间里自慰
I mean, we could masturbate in separate rooms.
-老天啊  -不 现在很流行的
- Oh, God! - No. It's quite modern.
-不 得了吧  -或者... 或者...
- No. Come on! - Or... Or...
就看在往日情分 最后一次
Just, for old times' sake, last one.
绝对是最后一次
Absolute last one.
我可以就古板地...
I could just, you know, the old traditional...
仅仅... 插进去
simply... stick it in.
没错 就像加油站 对吧
Yeah. Like a gas station, right?
就只是插进去
Just stick it in.
法国医生 是吧
So a French doctor, huh?
听起来你根本配不上这么好又有趣的人
She sounds far too nice and interesting for you.
她也没那么好
She's not that nice.
内心深处她... 就是个沉迷于地位和金钱的人 像你一样
Deep down she's... status- and money-obsessed. Like you.
这真不错
This is nice.
像朋友一样交谈
This is like being friends.
你懂的
You know.
是吉尔
It was Gil.
他很感兴趣
He's very interested.
我觉得你该加入我们
I think you should do this.
你很性感 你现在...
You're hot, you're...
真的太性感了
so hot right now.
得了 纳特
Come on. Nate.
我们应该做好人
We should be good people.
我懂
Uh, I know.
明天一早醒来发现自己并不是一团糟...
Wouldn't it be nice to just wake up in the morning and...
...这难道不好吗
...not feel like a fucking piece of shit?
-早 小西  -早
- Hey, Shiv. - Morning.
你知道昨晚棒极了 对吧
You know you're amazing, right?
也许是吧
Uh, yeah. I guess.
来见见吉尔吧
Come meet Gil.
他并不是个空想家 他会一路高歌的
He's not a pipe dream. He's gonna go all the way.
好吧
Ok.
我们挺守规矩的
So, we behaved ourselves.
他们应该写首歌赞美我们的美好品质
They're gonna write songs about how good we were.
小西 你就是只金发野兽
Shiv? You're a blonde beast.
你应该为所欲为
You should do whatever you want.
再见 纳特
Bye, Nate.
我觉得局势会很紧迫 但...
I think it's gonna be tight, but, uh...
所有的变量都站我们这边
you know, all the variables swing our way.
没错
Huh.
怎么了 杰西
Hey, what's up, Jess?
西诺亚小姐正等在线上
I have Ms. Shinoya on the line.
好的
Ok.
萨丽塔
Sarita?
喂
Hello?
伊罗娜 伊罗娜 你好 身体还好吗
Ilona. Ilona, hi. How are you?
天呐 听到你的声音我很高兴
God, it's great to hear your voice.
你起来了 你... 你收到我的礼物了吗
Y-You're up. Um, did... did you get my gift?
收到 我听我女儿说 你不想让我
Yes. So, my daughter told me you don't want me voting
在今天的董事会上投票 对吗
in today's board meeting. Is that right?
不 不 不 完全... 完全不是这样
No, no, no. That's... That's not it at all.
是...
That's, um...
能让我解释下吗 那是...
C-Can I explain? That's...
好吧 我想告诉你
Well, I'm letting you know
我会打电话参与表决
that I will be dialing in.
好吧 听着 有些事情
O-OK. Well, look, there's some issues.
我知道你还没...
I know you haven'...
听着 我... 我能不能过来跟你谈谈
Look, could I... Could I come and talk it through?
肯德尔 我会直接打电话表决的
Kendall, I will be dialing in.
我一小时内到
I'll be there in an hour.
很好 好的 谢谢 伊罗娜
Great. OK, thanks, Ilona.
你要跑那么远去找她吗 去长岛
You're gonna go all the way out to her? To Long Island?
-是的 我能...  -有时间吗
- Yeah, I can... - Is there time?
我能搞定 我能搞定
I can make it. I can make it.
我觉得...
I think...
我必须去这一趟
I think I have to go.
你准备好了吗 我们走
Hey. You ready? Let's go.
抱歉 罗伊先生 航道关闭了
Sorry, Mr. Roy, the skies are closed.
目前暂时限制飞行 可能有恐怖威胁
Temporary flight restriction. There's a possible terror threat.
不 不 我必须走 伙计
No, no, I need to go, pal.
他们罚多少我都出 快走
I'll pay whatever fine they hit us with. Let's go.
不能这么做 先生 联邦航空局会吊销我的驾照
We can't do that, sir. FAA will pull my license.
那好 联邦航空局那边我来解决
Uh, OK, I'll handle the FAA.
或是... 什么来着 直升飞机协会 我来解决
Or... What is it? The AHS? I'll handle it.
你有任何经济损失 我无限期补偿你 行吗
Whatever you lose financially, I'll make up in perpetuity. OK?
先生 如果我们现在起飞 可能会被F-16击落
Sir, if we take off now, we can be shot down by an F-16.
是 但也不一定啊 对吗
Yeah, but not really. Right?
空域被封锁了
Airspace is on lockdown.
我们没有任何办法
There's nothing we can do.
多久能回市里 金融区
How long to get to the city? Financial district?
老兄 我们应该喝一轮 是吧
Man, we should get a round of fuckin' shots going, right?
去准备吧
Make it happen.
马上就好
Will do.
能见到战犯还挺不错的 清理得很干净
It's nice to see the war criminal. Cleans up well.
是啊 人不错 很可爱
Yeah, nice guy, lovely guy.
那咱们没问题吧 关系多铁啊 是吧
We good, then? Solid? Right?
我听说洛根就算股骨碎了
I heard Logan started on time even when
阿斯彭: 以滑雪场而著称 富人聚居区和度假胜地
要从阿斯彭飞回来 也要准时开会
he was airlifted in from Aspen with a shattered femur.
是这样的
That is true.
可不是嘛
Yep, no.
就是那样
That is correct.
你的电话能用吗
Hey, is your phone working?
我能叫个摩托车快递小哥啥的吗
C-C-Can I get like a motorcycle courier?
啥都行 你能给办公室打个电话吗
Anything? Can you call your office?
抱歉 没信号
Sorry, no bars.
证券交易所外的每条路
They're evacuating five blocks
都被清了五个街区
each way from the Stock Exchange.
...曼哈顿下城区 纽约市警察局关闭了
...lower Manhattan. NYPD has shut down
-西侧高速...  -格丽 能听到吗
- the West Side Highway... - Gerri. Can you hear me?
你在哪里
Hey, where are you?
听着 我... 我...
Hey, listen, I'm... I'm...
我马上就到了
I'm almost there.
但交通停滞了 你先拖一拖
The traffic's stopped. I need you to stall.
什么 你说什么
What? What's that?
信号不好
It's a bad connection.
我听不清楚
I can't really hear you.
格丽
Gerri?
我在隧道里
I'm in a tunnel.
明白吗 拖延
OK? Stall.
好吧 你还有多远...
Well, how far are y...
我...
Uh, I...
靠
Shit.
怎么了
What?
他堵在路上了
He's in traffic.
别啊 千万别
Don't. Don't do this.
他问我们能拖多久
He's asking us how long can we stall.
-操 操 操  -"棒呆了"
- Fuck, fuck, fuck. - Great.
马上就好 他不会太迟的
It'll be all right. He's not gonna be too late.
-他来了  -早上好啊 早上好
- Here he comes. - Morning, morning.
早上好
Good morning.
-大家都到齐了  -是啊
- Oh! Quite a turnout. - Yeah.
弗兰克 你能让我们快点完工吗
Frank, will you whip us through?
我... 我刚得到消息
Uh, I... I just got word.
肯德尔可能会晚点到
I think Kendall will be a few minutes late.
要晚点开始吗
Request for a late start?
-不用  -不吗
- No! - No?
他能赶上 臭小子 他在哪儿
He can catch up. Fuck that! Where is he?
堵在路上了 我就知道这么多
Stuck in traffic. That's all I know.
好的 来吧 来吧 我们开始
OK, come on, come on, let's go. Let's go.
好 好
Yup, yup.
现在是中午十二点 我宣布
It's twelve noon, and I'd like to call
韦斯达·罗伊科股东大会正式开始
the meeting of Waystar Royco to order.
-点名  -什么... 点名
- Roll call. - What...? Roll call?
洛根·罗伊 你到了
Logan Roy. Yeah. You're here.
我们从来没点过名 点名算怎么回事
We've never done roll call. What is roll call?
-我们今天要点名  -为什么要点名
- We're doing it today. - Why are we doing roll call?
因为会就是这样开的 对吗 诺亚
Because that's how we do it. Right, Noah?
洛根·罗伊到了...
So Logan Roy is here...
弗兰克·弗农 到场
Frank Vernon. Present.
肯德尔·罗伊 缺席
Kendall Roy, absent.
-罗曼·罗伊  -在呢
- Roman Roy. - Yo.
尤恩·罗伊缺席
Ewan Roy, absent.
伊罗娜·西诺亚缺席
Ilona Shinoy, absent.
-塔图·卡萨玛  -到场
- Datu Kassma. - Present.
-戴维·斯万  -在
- Dewi Swann. - Here.
-保罗·钱伯斯  -乐于参加
- Paul Chambers. - Happy to be here.
-阿沙·卡恩  -到
- Asha Kahn. - Here.
-劳伦斯·易  -到
- Lawrence Yee. - Here.
先生
Sir!
-斯图伊·侯赛因  -我在这
- Stewy Hosseini. - I am here.
主席先生 够法定人数了
Mr. Chairman, we have a quorum.
我们还要欢迎令人尊敬的总顾问
Uh, we also welcome our esteemed general counsel
格丽·吉尔曼到会 谢谢格丽
Gerri Killman to the meeting. Thanks, Gerri.
大家手中都有一份议程
So everybody has a copy of the agenda
以及上次会议的纪要
and the minutes of the last meeting.
-没错吧  -没错
- Is that right? - Yes.
有人在看过之后
Do any of you have any questions
对此有任何疑问吗
that have come to you immediately after looking at them?
我这里有一些想法...
I know that I-I have a few thoughts...
大家需要看一看
we might have to take a look at.
什么想法
What thoughts?
稍等一下我翻到它
Just wait a second and I'll get to it.
好啊 是谁来了
OK. Who's this?
尤恩 这...
Ewan? Well...
你就是不能离远点 是吧
you just can't keep away, huh?
我想我应该露一次面
Thought maybe I'd show up for once.
看看戏
Watch the fun.
很高兴你能参加
Great to have you.
没有通行证
They wouldn't let me in downstairs
楼下不让我进来
without a passport.
已经开始了吗
Has it started?
肯德尔 你在哪
Kendall. Hey, where are ya?
我们已经开始了 老兄
We've already started, man.
我们开始了
We've started.
让杰西给我接通会议视频 听到了吗
Hey. Tell Jess to put me through the Polycom. Yeah?
那让我们继续请看第3条第1款
So, let's move along to item 3.1.
弗兰克
Frank.
"履职问题"是什么 太他妈含糊了
What's "Performance issues?" Sounds fucking vague.
它为什么在流行榜单上排位那么高
And why is it so high on the fuckin' hit parade?
我不知道我们今天是否
I don't know if we're actually
要去讨论那些 不如跳过它们吧
gonna hit those today. Maybe we can bump those.
抱歉 我一会打给你
Sorry, I'm gonna have to get back to you.
我们能跳过这些吗
Can we bump 'em?
好 那我们跳过
OK, then. Let's bump it.
这他妈的干什么呢
Ohh. What the fuck's goin' on?
我想肯德尔想要发表意见
I think Kendall wants to make a comment.
他有... 有件事要说...
He has a... a thing that he's going to speak...
而且伊罗娜也会打进来
I think Ilona is going to phone in, too.
他在线上 我在接通
He's on the line. I'm putting him through.
这是什么 这他妈什么鬼玩意
What is this? What the fuck is this?
你好 肯德尔
Hi, Kendall?
大家好 能听到我吗
Hey, guys. Can you hear me?
我诚挚道歉
I apologize.
我马上就到
I will be there shortly.
我们说到哪了
Where are we at?
我们在讨论你的条款
We are at your item.
履职问题
Performance issues.
你想我们等你吗
You want us to wait?
你在哪
Where are you?
去他妈的 我们要继续了
Fuck that. We're movin' on.
格丽 诺亚
Gerri, Noah,
如果我们想中断程序直到...
if we wanted to halt proceedings until...
不能中断程序
We're not halting proceedings.
-我们要继续了  -不 不 没关系 没关系
- We're moving on. - No, no. It's OK. It's OK.
我可以
I can do this.
老爸 这是大事
Dad, this is big.
是这样的...
Look...
我爱我的父亲
I love my father.
明白吗 我父亲是个传奇
OK? My father is a legend.
我十分敬仰他
I worship the ground he walks on.
没有什么能有损于
Nothing will ever detract
他一手建立的帝国
from what he's built and what he's done.
但他现在的身体状况不再适合管理公司
But he is currently unfit to run this company.
声音大点 我听不到
Speak up. I can't hear.
不仅因为他不肯花时间
Not only because of his refusal to take the time
好好休养大病初愈的身体
to recover from serious health issues,
还因为他一直不肯退休
but because every day he refuses to retire,
他马上就要亲手毁掉自己的传奇了
he is one day closer to destroying his own legacy.
他欠了大量外债
He took on levels of debt
甚至威胁到了公司的存亡
that threatened the very existence of our firm,
他在一个他曾经了解
he is lining up dead-weight acquisitions
但如今毫无经济效益的领域
in a sector that he has a historic regard for
安排自我拖累的收购
but which is a non-growth area.
我们面对的是一场事关存亡的硬仗
We face existential battles in scale,
但他朝向完全错误的方向
and he is facing precisely the wrong direction.
他在给一个
He is making decisions
他不再了解的未来做决定
for a future that he no longer understands,
我们没有犯错的机会了
and we don't have time for missteps.
错一步要花十... 两到三年的时间调整
What used to take ten... two, three years.
我们这块冰盖就要融化了
Our entire ice cap will melt.
他把我们最后的资金赌在
He is gambling our last dollars at the track
一匹就要被抬进胶厂[死亡]的马身上
on a horse that's ready for the glue factory,
我希望可以对他总统和主席的身份
and I am calling for a vote of no confidence in him
进行不信任投票
as CEO and chairman.
一通屁话 不行
Bullshit. No.
恐怕作为投票对象
I'm afraid since you are the subject of the vote,
你得回避了 洛根
you need to recuse yourself, Logan.
天呐 我他妈在浪费时间看戏吗
Oh, Jesus Christ. Fuckin' amateur hour at the fuckin' circus.
你不能投票
You don't get to vote,
也不能发表任何言论 这就是事实
and you don't get to comment, is the situation.
你真的得离开会议室
You really should leave the room.
行 没问题 没问题 投吧
OK, fine. Fine. Vote.
请您先离开好吗
Would you mind?
同志们 他还在吗
Guys. Is he there?
他还在会议室吗
Is he still in the room?
我是个病人 我动不了 去他妈的投票
I'm sick. I can't move. Fuck that vote.
他不能待在那 懂吗 同志们...
He can't be in the room. OK? Guys...
让会议记录记上一笔
Let the minutes reflect
洛根·罗伊被要求离开会议室
that Logan Roy was asked to recuse himself.
会议记录记上一笔 洛根·罗伊
Let the minutes reflect that Logan Roy
冲着弗兰克的大屁股狠踹了一脚
shoved his boot up Frank's ass.
好吧
Ok.
请所有赞成洛根·罗伊不信任投票的举手
All in favor of the vote of no confidence in Logan Roy?
我赞成 我举手了
Me. My hand is raised.
更多是出于悲伤而非愤怒
More in sorrow than in anger.
少假慈悲了 犹大
Oh, no shit, Judas.
弗兰克
Frank!
见到你回来真好
Nice to see you back.
阿沙
Asha?
我看到你了
I see you.
我也看到你了 洛根
And I see you, Logan.
老天爷啊 我他妈简直不敢相信
Oh, Jesus, this is just un-frickin'-believable.
斯图伊 斯图伊
Stewy? Stewy.
我 好吧
Me. OK.
听我说 作为一个大股东
Listen, as a major shareholder,
鉴于当前形势还不够清晰
and in the absence of any real clarity here,
我觉得
I think it's the view
这是一件家务事 我弃权
that this is a family matter and abstain.
-反对  -强烈反对
- Against. - Strongly against.
伊罗娜在线上
We have Ilona on the line.
你好 洛根 好的
Hello, Logan. Yes.
在跟我的家人磋商之后
After consulting with my family,
我投票支持动议
I am voting in favor of the motion.
谢谢你八辈祖宗 伊罗娜
Thanks for nothin', Ilona.
滚吧
Fuck off.
尤恩
Ewan?
投吧
Go ahead.
现在票数多少了 4比2吗
What are we on, 4-2?
投啊
Go on.
来啊 鼠窝欢迎你
Yeah. Join the rats.
来做个了结吧
Let's finish this, huh?
我投票支持洛根
I vote with Logan.
我觉得我们该趁着所有股东都在的时候
I think we should take the time to consider this properly
好好考虑一下这件事
when all parties are here.
塔图 我们现在表决
Datu, we're voting now.
洛根 拜托 你能别参与讨论吗
Logan, please, can you stay out of the conversation?
在这种情况下 洛根 我支持洛根
In which case, Logan. I stick with Logan.
肯德尔 你隔着电话数数了吗
Kendall, you counted right there?
你数清楚了吗
You all right?
四票对四票 你就这点能耐吗
Four against four, this is your best shot?
劳伦斯
Lawrence?
肯德尔 我不掺和这件事
I don't have a dog in this fight, Kendall.
我弃权
I abstain.
那么 目前而言
So, currently
我们有四票支持洛根继续掌权
we've got four votes in favor of Logan to remain,
四票要求洛根下任 两票弃权
four of stepping down, two abstentions.
格丽
Uh, Gerri.
你想就在场的
Do you want to say anything
资深管理团队的态度说上两句吗
to speak to the senior management teams' attitudes here?
-关上...  -各位都知道
- Shut the... - Well, you know,
我是独立观察员
I'm an independent observer,
不参与投票 一个总顾问
non-voting, a general counsel,
所以我不适合发表任何意见
so I'm not sure that's appropriate?
好吧 谢谢
Right. Thanks.
非常...
Very...
专业
professional.
罗曼
Hey, Roman?
Roman.
兄弟 举手啊
Put your hand up, bro.
罗曼 听得到我说话吗
Roman, can you hear me?
你举手了吗
Is your hand up?
肯德尔 你听得到吗
Kendall, yeah. Hey. Are you there?
罗曼...
Roman...
你那边信号不好
Uh, you're kind of cuttin' out.
罗曼...
Roman...
他断线了
He's off the line.
快点吧 儿子
Come on, son.
罗曼
Roman.
快点 快点 快点
Come on. Come on, come on.
你最好想想清楚 罗慕路斯
You better be smelling your fuckin' armpit, Romulus.
我觉得很难选 你懂吗
I think it's a tough one, you know?
我觉得...
I think, uh...
-太难选了 但也许...  -罗曼支持我
- It's tough, but maybe... - Roman for me.
这样可不能算支持你吧
I'm not sure we can count that for you.
-罗曼  -反对投票
- Roman? - Against.
他投了 还能临时变卦吗
He s-started to vote, I'm not sure he can change that.
-他当然可以随便改  -你不该待在这里
- He can fucking change. - You shouldn't be here,
你不该在这发号施令 你该待在会议室外面
you shouldn't be speaking here, you should be out of this room.
-这是非法的  -随你哔哔
- This is illegal. - Whatever.
如果不算他 就陷入僵局
If you count 'em out, deadlock.
继续掌权 老子还是主席
Continuity prevails. I'm chairman.
决定性一票 我赢了 你他妈没戏唱了
Casting vote. I win. It's fucking over!
投票怎么样了
What's the vote?
我的儿
My son.
你就这点子能耐了
That was your best shot.
你输了
You lost.
我觉得他输赢与否还有待商榷...
I think there's some doubt as to whether he lost...
肯德尔 弗兰克 阿沙 伊罗娜
And Kendall, Frank, Asha, Ilona,
被逐出董事会 你们被炒了 立刻滚蛋
off the board, fired with immediate effect.
我觉得你无权这么做
I don't think you're able to do that.
安保
Security!
我他妈正在摆正一艘油轮
I am in the middle of turning a fucking tanker.
-弗兰克 你被炒了  -我还有些疑问...
- Frank, you're fired. - I have some doubt...
我他妈正在摆正一艘油轮
I'm in the middle of turning a fucking tanker!
你听到了吗
Do you hear?!
弗兰克 你被炒了
Frank! You're fired.
什么都不准带 滚蛋
Without exit package.
阿沙 再见
Asha, goodbye.
哪个谁给伊罗娜发个邮件过去
Somebody send a telegram to Ilona
告诉她 我们不再需要她
telling her she's no longer required,
我祝她早日战胜病魔
and my best to her cancer.
我觉得我们都需要花点时间捋一捋
I think we all need to take a beat.
-你说啥 风太大 听不见  -洛根 闭嘴
- Meh meh meh fuckin' meh. - Logan, stop.
股价这么疲软的时候
Is it wise to fire the board
开除大半个董事会
with the share price this weak,
一头扎进政治斗争 真的明智吗
heading into a political fight?
别他妈不服输 你出局了
Take it like a fucking man. You're out.
你完蛋了 你想搞死我 结果弄巧成拙
You're fucked. You tried to kill me, but you failed.
把你自己搞死了 现在快滚吧
And you're dead. Now fuck off!
来吧 哭给我看
Oh, go on, cry me a river.
快他妈滚犊子
Get the fuck out.
直接滚出去 注销通行证
Straight out! Passes canceled.
我们会把各位的物品寄到府上
We'll send along personal belongings.
需要拿几样东西也不行吗
Just need to get some things, OK?
再也不见 谢谢
No goodbyes! Thank you!
你他妈放开我
Get your fuckin' hands off me.
我他妈该拿你这混小子怎么办
And what the fuck am I gonna do with you?
老爸 我也不知道
I don't know, Dad.
天呢
Jesus.
-我能拿点东西走吗  -不行
- Can I just get some stuff? - No. No.
-谢谢  -好的
- Thank you. - OK.
天啊 简直是地狱之旅
God, that was the journey from hell.
出租车整整半小时挪不动道
Spent 30 minutes in a cab not moving.
亲爱的
Honey?
汤姆
Tom?
-回来了  -你还好吧 亲爱的
- Hey. Hey. - Hey. You OK, sweetheart?
还好 我觉得有人给我下毒了
Yeah. I think somebody poisoned me.
我在家工作来着
I'm working from home.
有人给你下毒了呀
Oh, someone poisoned you?
-对啊  -在酒里下的毒吗
- Hmm. - Oh! With booze?
-你好哇  -你好
- Hey. Hey. - Hey.
我给你带了礼物
OK, I got you something.
-谢谢  -我想你了
- Oh, thank you. - I missed you.
你才离家十四个小时而已
You only been away, like, 14 hours.
对啊 这么想你 真是我的错呢
Yeah, well, sorry for missing you.
什么事
Yeah. What?
什么鬼
What the fuck?
怎么了 出什么事了
What? What's happened?
说仔细点 再仔细点
Well, more. T-Tell me more.
怎么回事 发生了吗
What's happened? Did it happen?
好 立刻回我电话
OK, call me right back.
灭霸要打响指了
The world's blown up.
我操
Oh, fuck!
你说"发生了吗"是几个意思
What do you mean, "Has it happened"?
-你知道吗  -什么 我不知道
- Did you know? - What? No!
-智障肯德尔  -发生了吗
- Fuckin' Kendall! - Has it happened?
发... 发生了吗
Did... Has it happened?
等会儿
Wait!
肯德尔 回我电话
Kendall? Call me back.
-你知道吗  -知道啊
- You knew? - Yeah.
我觉得喝了太多有点烧心
I think too much "Abolgoll" hurt my tummy.
康纳 你听说了吧
Connor. You heard?
听说了啊 肯德尔发起老爹的不信任投票
Yeah, Kendall called for a vote of no confidence on Dad.
肯德尔 还有谁他妈的知道这事
Kendall? Who the fuck else knew about this?
-罗曼知道  -罗曼知道吗
- Roman did. - Roman knew?
我不知道你还期望有什么不同
I don't know why you'd expect anything different.
全他妈把我蒙在鼓里
Not a single one of them told me about this.
全他妈乱套了
It's complete bullshit.
小西 你知道我不喜欢选边站队
Oh, Shiv, you know I don't like to take sides.
不过这次我站你这边
But I'm on your side.
滚蛋
Fuck you.
-你知道吗  -我知道 我试着联系你来着
- You knew? - Yeah, I tried to call you.
-那你还打得不够多  -我试过了
- Not hard enough. - I did!
-他开了半个董事会的人  -肯德尔怎么样了
- He's fired half the board. - What about Kendall?
-被开了 弗兰克 阿沙 通通滚犊子了  -什么
- Fired. Frank, Asha, fired. - What?
叛军在城里的广场上被屠戮殆尽了
The rebels are getting shot in the town square.
汤姆 待会儿再回来跟你算账
I'll talk to you later, Tom.
我们是叛军吗
Are we the rebels?
-什么事  -白宫打来电话
- Yes? - I have the White House.
您接通电话时 总统会亲自跟您谈话
The president will join once you're on.
他们想表示诚挚的歉意
They're very apologetic.
-跟他说我在线上  -好的 先生
- Tell him I'm on. - Yes, sir.
是的 他在线上
Yes, he's on.
您好 总统先生 他将即刻与您对话
Hello, Mr. President. He'll be with you momentarily.
他马上就来
He'll be right there.
谢谢您
Thank you.
总统先生
Mr. President.
好多了 好太多了
Oh, much, much better.
不用道歉
No need for an apology.
看来恐怖袭击把您搞得焦头烂额
Well, you really had a terrorist problem.
我刚刚亲自拿下了一个恐怖分子呢
I've just taken down a terrorist myself.
我儿子
My son.
您能帮我省掉美国联邦通讯委员会的那些繁文缛节吗
So, can you help me with this FCC red tape bullshit?
您也是 总统先生
And you, Mr. President.
THE SUB-MAN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠